Blood Demon Arts.
Exploding Blood!
No one can break
my bond with Nezuko!
Nezuko.
Nezuko!
I won.
I beat him.
Dad helped me.
Somehow, our family heirloom,
the kagura dance,
helped me to unleash this move.
But anyway, it helped me
and I could beat him.
What?
Nezuko looks blurry.
Is it because I took too many breaths?
My ear is ringing so hard.
It's painful all over my body.
I must
recover fast.
I have to keep fighting.
I must save Inosuke.
Quickly!
The smell of blood is getting stronger.
Which reminds me…
I don't smell the ashes.
Could it be…
I clearly chopped his head off.
Do you think you can defeat me?
What a pity.
Are you feeling happy
in that pathetic delusion of yours?
I severed my head with my thread
before you could chop off my head.
That's it.
I'm going to kill you and your sister.
I've never been so angry for so long.
Stand up.
Stand up now.
Adjust your breath.
Quickly! Hurry!
How on earth did you not get burnt?
Only me and my threads got burnt.
Is it because of your sister?
But thanks to you, I'm getting irritated.
I can break you into pieces
without the slightest regrets.
If I use the correct breathing technique,
it'll make no difference
because of how exhausted I am.
Blood Demon Arts.
Murderous Eye Basket.
Don't be impatient.
Keep your breath in check.
Calm down.
Just calm down.
I can't raise my hand.
Someone is coming.
Is it Zenitsu?
You did a good job holding out
until I got here.
Leave the rest to me.
One after another,
human scums
just keep on getting in my way!
Blood Demon Arts.
Cutting Thread Rotation.
Total Concentration Breathing.
Breath of Water.
Eleventh Form.
Dead Calm.
Eleventh Form?
So what even if it's Eleventh Form?
What?
What? What did he do?
The moment my threads got near him,
they all snapped.
Not a single thread caught him?
Did he just cut the toughest threads?
This can't be happening!
One more time!
I've made a mistake!
I've been the only one
who did no wrong all along
in this pretend family.
We got you now.
Hey. Look over there.
Is it a demon?
A kid demon.
He may look like a child,
but he's still a demon.
If we let him be, he'll eat someone.
Hey.
Do you want me to save you?
Are you willing to listen to my request?
Yes, I'll do anything!
I'll do as you say! So just save me!
Well, will you be part of my family?
Yes, I will!
What are you talking about?
Now, prepare yourself.
Welcome.
From now on, you are part of my family.
Drink this.
Our whole family obtained
our powers from Rui.
We were all weak demons.
We received our powers from Rui.
That person favored Rui so much
that he allowed him to do so.
Do you feel it?
You don't have to fear
demon slayers anymore.
Well then, on to our final step.
Lift your head.
Congratulations.
You're now a real member of my family.
We are just a pretend family.
We weren't related by blood.
We are a family
that is being put together.
I'm sorry!
I won't mess up again.
I'll work harder, Rui!
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't try hard enough.
Sometimes, I turn back to normal.
Don't give me excuses, Mom.
Be a good mom for me.
I understand, Rui.
We're all afraid of demon slayers.
We just wanted some comrades.
In fact, I didn't sign up to play
this baffling pretend family game.
But whoever disobeys
Rui's demands or orders
will be cut into shreds,
stripped off their minds,
and hanged to be exposed to the sun.
I can't take it anymore.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
You're not that stupid, are you?
You're different from the rest.
Let's escape.
It's because of you that I could say this.
I'm treating only you like my real sister.
Tomorrow, the lord
will summon Rui downhill.
That's when we can run for it.
Too bad.
They may be fools, but I'm not.
But I still made a mistake!
Rui.
Mom got killed.
I think our big brother
got killed as well.
What should we do?
The demon slayers are coming.
Hey.
Should we escape?
No.
You should have known.
I hate it when you turn your face
back to normal.
What are you looking at?
There's nothing to see here.
I was lucky to get away
with just scratches on my face.
A demon!
What the hell?
It's useless.
You can't cut it.
My yarn may look soft,
but it is indeed tenacious.
First, the solvent will dissolve
the clothes out of the way.
And then, it will dissolve you.
You're going to be my glutinous meal
in no time.
You're amazing.
You can make threads with your hands.
Good evening.
The moon is beautiful tonight.
Looks like you don't want
to get along with me.
Wait.
Please!
I had to do it because I was ordered.
If I resist, I'll be cut into shreds.
I see.
That's a pity.
I can help you.
Can we get along?
Are you going to help me?
Yes.
But in order for us to get along,
I have a few questions for you.
My sweet lady,
how many people have you killed?
Five.
But I was under his command,
so I can't help it.
You don't have to lie to me
because I know it all.
-I'm amazed by your spell that turned
-Help me!
one of our men into a cocoon.
You ate 80 people, right?
I didn't eat that many people.
I only killed five.
I came here from the west, you know.
My sweet lady, I said west.
I came here as I saw cocoons
hanging in the west of the mountain.
And those trapped in the cocoons
have all died and liquified.
In that spot alone,
I counted at least 14 cocoons.
Fourteen people had died in it.
But I'm not angry at you.
I'm only here to verify
the actual death toll.
Why do you have to do that?
You're going to be penalized accordingly
and be reborn!
Penalized?
That way, we can get along better.
If you're left unpunished
for taking people's lives,
there won't be any closure
for those you killed.
I'm going to gouge out your eyes,
cut your body open
and remove your innards.
For every person you killed,
I shall torture you.
After you suffer that pain and anguish,
you'll be absolved from your crimes.
Let's do our best, okay?
It's okay!
You're a demon.
You won't die or suffer any side effects.
You're kidding me!
Die, you bitch!
It looks like we're never
going to get along.
What a pity.
Breath of the Insect. Butterfly Dance.
Caprice.
My head didn't get chopped off.
That's the blade she's using?
I see.
Her arm isn't strong enough
because of her short stature.
So she couldn't chop off my head.
That means I can beat her.
Even if I didn't chop off your head,
you shouldn't have rest easy.
Because there are demon slayers like me
who use poison.
I'm the Demon Slayer Corps'
Insect Hashira,
Shinobu Kocho.
I may be the only Hashira
who's unable to decapitate demons.
Instead, I make poison
that's lethal to them.
That's quite impressive, don't you think?
I'm sorry.
You didn't hear that because you're dead.
How silly of me.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'll manage.
What about the demon?
Shouldn't you chop her head off?
I killed her with wisteria toxin.
She's already dead,
so she'll just rot away later.
I'm a pharmaceuticals expert!
Your clothes are all dissolved.
But your body is left unscathed.
That's great.
Now then,
I'm curious to know where the demon
who enslaved this lady is.
But it looks like Mr. Tomioka
is already one huge step ahead of me.
Nezuko.
Kill.
I must kill those two.
Siblings…
What are you going to do, Rui?
What is family?
I don't know.
Because I don't have
any memory as a human.
Is that why you're asking us
to pretend to be your family?
I thought that by forming
a bond like a family,
I can recover my memories
and reminisce my bonds
with my real family.
That's right.
I…
Nezuko.
You're amazing!
You can make poison for demons.
I'm a student
of the pharmaceutical sciences.
You don't have to wield a sword
to be a demon slayer.
I see.
Here's a little gossip
from the Taisho era.
My poison is concocted in a scabbard.
Only my swordsmith and I
know how to concoct it.
All right, I'm going to shoot up the ranks
with a unique sword too!
I think you should first train
to keep your uniform from dissolving.
What a poisonous remark.
Next, episode 20, "Against Corps Rules."
It's good to be ambitious.
Let's do our best.
TO BE CONTINUED
Subtitle translation by CL Tan